are we turning what are we doing
let's be Rush
Hour must be rush
hour 4:30 God everybody just got out of
work it look like
hey
Missy how are
you camera looking
okay I hope
so it's always hard to
know I'm going the back route because
there's too many people
today just woke up yeah
you taking a nap or
you sometimes I'll take a nap before I
go on my bike ride which is kind of
[Music]
nice W lots of dirt hold your breath
oh my
God hey K what's
up what's
up
hi princess a she didn't laugh she she
a't kind to away with me
oh I smell rotting
tree yeah the smell of rotting tree I
smell
it those
mushrooms 824 an
am.
wow how's the camera
AIP it's quality okay I can't really
tell in my previewer
wow yep it's just my end of work
day visuals very good okay nice it's not
too too light or
something looks like it's
okay I'm using the pocket 3 today which
I I I feel like does a better job
with like
visuals yeah I thought about getting the
action five it came out
yesterday but it it's got the same
sensor as uh the
pocket
so I don't know if it's going to be
worth the money though it's another five
600 bucks I just spend that money on a
server
yeah I was doing the I updated the route
command so if you click on exclamation
point route or if you type exclamation
point route you'll get Goblin AB
bridged which has the shortened route
that I'm
doing
so you know the pack isn't that bad I've
got the pack back on today it really
isn't I mean all things considered I
think it's
fine I I actually reduced the battery
weight oh I forgot to turn my GPS
on my garment I always do
that I I'll get credit for the
ride that's actually something really
you see what I just did there I stood up
and instead of
my gear taking all the hit for the
vibration my body and my knees took the
hit
so seems to be a better way to do
that another thing too is I can just
walk around anywhere I I'm totally free
to just move about the cabin so to
speak I feel like it's a little bit
Overexposed for some reason doesn't it
seem a little light do it seem too
light it could be too
late maybe I'm just
crazy hey how's it going east coast
guy I feel like the I feel like the
image is a little bit too
bright could probably take it down one I
I don't know what the EV setting is I'm
might have it on the wrong
thing yeah I think you're right let me
go check it
all right don't look at my
nose confirm
exposure oh wow it's plus 7 evv yeah no
wonder hey why is it going sideways
yeah I don't know how I did
that yeah let's make
it make it back to zero did it did it f
the image
there it didn't
right I don't know why it's doing it's
like acting weird
give me a
second
betterer I want it in
zero how about that confirm
how's
that now the sh Shadows yeah they wer in
too
many
yeah all
right I I'm so happy I can preview the
picture now though I couldn't do that
before cuz they didn't have the battery
set up for my cam for my phone my phone
has unlimited battery now pretty
much so I can just leave the previewer
on and just watch it so if I get gray or
whatever actually see it whoa missed the
turn cuz I'm
talking yeah that's much better that
image is much better
it is a gorgeous day
today one of the best ones ever it's
been a great day hey how are you
hey I'm wearing my
uniform my adventure guy uniform
RTI is on isn't
it did I forget God there's like things
I always forget one of
them all right let me I'll around right
now me get down this
hill there we
go could not retrieve the bellum's B
location okay fine all right hold your
horses wait why is it
gray oh I know why it's gray because the
starlink all of a sudden crapped
out
yeah the starlink was like kicking ass
and then and then all of a sudden there
trees and the start like what is up with
these
trees so I don't know what what's worth
having staric pick
up when there's no
trees and then having Grays when it
transfers or just having and not do
that there it goes again
see
L you got the plane
though that's good
uh oh starlink
is not working very well right
now at
all
nope starink is on zero right now I
don't know why I wonder if starink got
turned off I'm going to check the
starlink I think the vibration might be
turning a starlink off and on I know you
guys are annoyed by that but I am paying
the money for it so I want to make sure
it works
and if you know it's I I did something
different with the Starling
today so I got to make sure oh there it
comes it's just not doing very well it's
definitely picking it up it's just not
very
well
yeah it's coming
back slowly but
surely don't call me
surely mini Goblin I'm doing a bridge
Goblin exclamation point
route has the new
one I'm not coming to sh out I wish
I will promise you this Mark I talked to
my wife yesterday at
dinner and on critical mass Friday which
is next
Friday I will go to Charlotte that's the
one day I will promise you I'm always
going to
Charlotte because it just makes sense
right it's critical mass you know I can
bike all the way to
Charlotte I can do critical mass and
then I can turn around and have my wife
give me a right
home yeah
next next
Friday for me it's actually no different
it's actually
shorter that's not true Charlotte is 30
something miles I think
32 this route that I do is 25
miles what is critical mass critical
mass is a a group bike
ride everybody gets together and
sort of celebrates bike commuting and
everything bike
culture they kind of become annoying to
the motorists though
right because
they they take over they take over the
roads critical mass meaning they they
they they don't let cars pass them or
anything there's like hundreds of bikers
bikers on the
road you know
what are we doing we're doing stuff are
we going what I was going to go that way
I should have signaled but none of them
signal either so I don't feel bad
this is so
annoying God Road
bikers why is it that some people have
to be so
annoying with their bik their cars have
to be
loud their bikes have to be loud did you
hear how loud that bike
was your bike doesn't have to be that
loud
I just don't get it that's all it's fine
if you want to do that I just don't get
it it's an Amazon
person this I'm going to brought you by
Amazon
Prime we don't just have
Vans we drive cars too
how is not letting people
pass no
idea honestly I go because
it's a celebration of everybody who
likes to ride their bike and it's kind
of
fun it's really it's really visually
interesting looks like I'm turning
around
lots of lots of returning home traffic
no header is
fun you know and there's a lot of people
in my stream who like loud cars and and
I that's fine I just don't I absolutely
do not I think it's
annoying I don't like loud anything you
can call me old but I like did quiet I
[Laughter]
almost NV de people I don't but
sometimes I do I really love music of
course maybe that's why
CU that's not music at all I wonder if
people who like loud cars also have no
sense of Music at
all I bet you that's true well you
generally is because they're the ones
who crank absolute on the radio
that's not a commentary on the genre
that's
like if you really think that the entire
world wants to hear your
song Let me just I'm going to inform you
of
something they
don't they really don't they really
don't give a
and nobody there is not a single
person on the planet who thinks you're
cool for making me hear your favorite
music
if they go to my twitch Channel that's
different they chose to be
there I didn't choose to hear your
blaring absolute tasting
music
hi I don't know you know what this is
the thing okay I actually think St I
think starlink might be hurting this
Starck keeps trying to take
over the algorithm is like I can see it
it's like the modems kind of fight with
the
starlink when the starlink has a clear
sky it's like hey I got
this you
know and but right now the starlink is
totally zero
because there's
trees sometimes I wonder if the Starling
gets turned off from the vibrations on
accident
somehow we'll find
out I wish I could put all that data on
the screen I totally would I would I
would let you guys help
me I don't think it's bouncing well I
don't
I think the reason might be too because
the I think the starlink is has a higher
much higher latency than the
others and so when it tries to
reassemble all the
packets I think it's it's having to wait
around for the Starling stuff it's got
all these packets and then you end up
getting a
tear so it doesn't have the packet in
time to show it I should probably turn
up the
delay that lets it the caching server
like catch up
you can do
that boy I feel a lot faster today for
some reason maybe because I put air in
my tires that'll do
it I don't know
maybe I mean it could be
the computer at
home yeah who
knows might need to restart it
[Music]
it's always something though
huh see I would have
thought I would have thought the
Starling could have picked up more right
here
internet not available
[Music]
oh God
feel is the heart rate working my
battery's getting low
20 more
satellites seems like a lot
yeah in the red there
there
4,823 satellites in orbit wow
it's going to get worse
man these satellite Wars that have
lasers and take out other
ones I think they already have
that need a brake adjustment I feel like
sure is cozy
it seems like a lot of
satellites but that's where the future
communications
is you say they're trying to regulate it
more they're trying to attack Starling
because it has a
monopoly cuz Amazon hasn't got their
stuff off the ground
yet there supposed to be a competitor
eventually
eventually Space
X 12,00
wow
yeah
Green I'm trying to keep it nice and
happy I really hope we get in under two
hours today but I seriously doubt
it my right with GPS seems to think it's
going to estimate the 2 hours and 30
minutes that's what it
says we'll
see these Hills if you don't push up
them they take a long
time you know cuz you're not going very
fast
IP
address yeah they'll have to do
something
such a nice day though
it was weird I got up at like 5:00 a.m.
today cuz I fell asleep at like 10:00
11:00 I I redid
my plan to be that time
because I been feeling I got to be
falling asleep earlier all the time
now because it's just so easy
to get up and
go it works out though because I end up
coming home right when my wife gets home
usually
can't see her she was like motioning to
me the whole time I couldn't see
her making sure my St is still
melted oh
yeah I know that's why that's the main
reason I started wearing the rig
again s was never pay
attention the main reason I started
wearing the rig instead of putting on
the like is because it's going to get
dark and vibrations in darkness are
really really bad for
streaming they mess it up totally
yeah it does to get that
faster and but when it's on my body my
body dampens all the
vibration so it has almost no vibration
at
all that's why I can mountain bike with
it that's another reason I started
wearing it again it's like if I want to
do a Mountain Trail mountain bike trail
Trail one day I can just do
that you know
it's a big hill there
do you
over
yeah I mean that's the idea right is a
they just disintegrate when they come
back that's how you can clean them up
it's kind of
cool there's quite a bit of delay in the
video
feed the van just passed
trying to keep
a consistent 180 190 Watts
my as
Amazon oh God I don't know I've been
buying groceries out there
lately yeah I bought $50 worth of fresh
produce last
week for my smoothies and
stuff pretty good
I bring it right to your door frozen
food
even put right
away it's pretty
nice food from Amazon yeah it was
fantastic I think it probably cost a
little more
I don't know I haven't compared the
prices yet
but I'm going to do it
again it just saves me
time a lot of
time plus I I like that I can just you
know click on a reorder button and know
the stuff that I need right away I'm not
the kind of person to like browse around
when I go dropping I don't like
that a lot of people do
though chicken with the truck
yeah I've heard this so cars yeah I've
heard
that I haven't ever done it I don't
that's something I probably wouldn't
do but
yeah I think you're right
yeah I know I pushed hard on that
one yeah
yeah all right let's come back down let
me rest I knew I had this downhill here
still it's better to keep it low than to
spike and come
back when you spike you burn a match or
two and if you keep it low you never
burn
matches I don't want to be burning
matches
that's what they call
it everybody depending on the BO2 Max
they've got so many matches they can
burn in a given
event on a Sprint or
something my problem is is that my heart
rate has it's gotten better but I'm
older so it recovers a little bit slower
than it used to I'm back to green now
though so
[Music]
heric
carditis I don't know what that is there
something to do with the heart heart
inflammation I hope
not some kind of concert going on back
there they're getting ready for it's
Friday night oh my God there's parties
and stuff I forgot it's Friday I don't
know why I thought it was Thursday for
some reason
I just didn't
register we are smooth
sailing PE
break not till
birdale I mean probably something going
on at burd
night I got no place to
be it's
Friday I'm not going to buy
a
bike I mean a home computer lab home lab
computer
until I get completely done with the
move I
decided it is this is my regular
route exclamation point route you can go
follow it's my
daily probably going to just keep it
that
way occasionally we'll do mountain bike
ride mountain bike rides take it out of
me though they're so hard on you hard on
your body hey how are
you
uhoh my stach is acting up give me a
second it's doing something weird yeah
[Music]
the strap
is rotating I I got
to zip tie that strap on there so it's
on there all the time so it doesn't
slide you
[Music]
know I should just do that right
now but I'll do that later I don't have
this
TI I'm going to cook my
hand in the
microwaves all
right everybody
[Music]
good all
right oh I had a my sandal was folding
down and I got a blister
damn ouch that hurt my PE
PE yeah those things should be illegal I
swear to that guy's doing 40 m hour on
an ebike and one of those e motocross
bikes they should be
illegal there's kids who shouldn't have
driver's licenses driving those like 40
mph
ebikes that look like motocross
bikes I think they should be totally
regulated people like they shouldn't be
regulated no they absolutely should plus
they're silent so you can't even hear
them coming here he comes he's going
past me right
now we go check it
out older harder and sand shape
absolutely
hey another Amazon Prime another segment
brought to you by Amazon
Prime give us all the trucks all the
vans
Brak new
shapes
yeah I'm I'm glad I got back to my base
weight earlier this year finally if you
know me you've been watching me for the
last four
years you know how big I was I got
really
big I'm back to a normal Rob makes me
very happy actually cuz I mean it was
hard to get back to it I've got out of
shade before and gotten back but this
time was really hard cuz I'm a lot
older there's uh do you guys know Battle
Star
Galactica the Remake anybody familiar
with
that the hot blonde the hot blonde sylon
robot
oh I got to change the bike
thing I took my mcal
off I put my 48 MLS
on my gravel tires my 80
lbs gravel 80 lbs of pressure grab
house I put this back
in so they're faster
I'm going to put
my I'm going to put my fenders my full
fenders back
on this
weekend so I can ride in the
rain without a
problem you know
[Music]
I think swimming is a great
exercise I don't think it's the most
healthy it's definitely an exercise you
can do until the end of your life I was
a big athlete in the 30s
in my 30s I loved
it I drowned myself trying to learn how
to
swim enough to do TR one it is pretty
healthy though for
sure I don't think it's the most healthy
though first of
all it doesn't do anything to
build joint health under stress or it's
actually really really bad for bone
density you need a little bit of running
to build bone density B your bones
transmit
vibration uh messages to your brain to
tell you to build that you need more
calcium so there's some of some weight
training and thing like that but cycling
doesn't do it either so it's a little
bit more
but I I think I think the best solution
is that actually kind of mix it up
obviously don't just do one thing all
the
time that's one of the reasons I got
into
Tron I think Triathlon
is probably the most healthy activity
you can do in terms of you know overall
health for your body because it hits
everything you get the the problem is
the running even though it builds bow
density it's murder on your knees my
knees
anyway yeah
the best exercise is the one you'll do
right that you
enjoy I think I enjoy cycling cycling is
very peaceful to me it gets me out yoga
I do yoga every
morning I I like yoga because it keeps
me limber and you need stuff like that
for your spine I'm a just I'm a licensed
yoga
instructor
did 16 14
was anyway I'm not licensed
anymore but so was my
wife I learned so much about human
anatomy in that yoga class because we
had to go through all this physical
therapy
training it was really
interesting I
think one of the most interesting
facts that I didn't comprehend was
they we had this woman who talked to us
about the science of
Aging she uh specializes
in uh therapeutic yoga for the
elderly and she used to have a saying
called build a
booty and she's she would is her Mantra
she would tell all her old people that
she works with the rest homes and stuff
if you one of the biggest things that
stops old people as they stop generating
muscle right well as soon as your booty
goes you can't walk
because you can't maintain your upright
posture anymore and at a certain point
you can't do you know the exercises
necessary to build your
booty and so she kept saying she's like
build a booty build a booty her her
opinion was the most important muscle
group to maintain over a long time into
into aging into Old AG is your
glutes above everything else because
they're your
stabilizers and it's the people who lose
them they lose their the ability to walk
just because they don't have it hey
thanks for the
fall um the other thing that she said
this is kind of a fun chat topic the
other thing she said I talked about this
yesterday the other thing that she said
was the number one problem with old
people in her experience as a PT person
for the elderly in retired home
is
uh the dehydration of all their tissues
I'm not talking about hydrate you know #
hydrate drink your water all the time
I'm talking about
combating old AG dehydration which
happens whether you drink water or
not
so and she showed the tissues she showed
she showed the the discs between your
spine column your your
vertebrae
and it was it was amazing it was like a
little sponge just dried up and didn't
have any water left in it and she said
and she well how do you fight that how
do you keep the the spongy you
know um tissues that connect your bones
not to mention your bones so those and
then she showed the bones and the bones
the bones look like they've been
grinding the spinal bones look like
they've been grinding against another
bone and they were all brittle and had
these kind of Splinter fractures all at
the bottom of them where they met the
other thing because of the abrasion and
stuff and for continue and she said I
mean it was kind of one of
those you know how they you know how
they have the Scared
Straight you know
driving movies to scare you into driving
correctly or they show you the safety
videos if you're in construction of
people getting crushed cuz they're not
paying attention they're really gory it
was kind of that
approach she was like she was like
showing the stuff and she and then she
goes you want to know how to avoid that
and I said yeah she goes you need to
move your spine
in every
direction for at least 20 seconds every
day and hold
it and she didn't mean extreme like you
know push it to the edge what you need
to do is she said she that's what she
said that's what yoga does and in that
sense yoga is physical
therapy so if you're especially if
you're doing if you're an old person
doing yoga or even young you should
integrate something that moves your
spine every way that it can be
moved for 10 to 20
seconds that is the that is the
secret to youth especially in your back
and if you look at yoga particular
Danga the primary series it does that
Mar Chas those are all spinal
rotation and then you've got the you've
got the like side body like side to side
things you know that's like curving it
from left it to the right
and then you
have of course then you have the back of
course the back bends you have the back
bends at the
end and those are hard you know it's
probably better to do like Crescent
where you go on your stomach and pull
your knees so you can you know bend your
back the reverse
Direction but yeah if you do if you do
yoga every day you the reason that yoga
is so good for the elderly above
everything besides with regard to to
hydration
is because it moves it it the way to
keep those spongy tissues hydrated is to
is to compress them and then uncompress
them because just like a sponge it
compresses them and then it soaks in
more
water and then it um and then it pulls
more water in fresh blood and stuff
liquids same thing with your organs by
the way when you twist your body safely
to a safe distance the way you do in
marasa and yoga you're liter Al ringing
out your organs your organs are getting
compressed as if you were ringing out a
sponge and you compress the bad the the
stale blood out of your organs and then
when you uncompress it sucks in a bunch
of new blood so blood pulls in your
capillaries and stuff like that and you
know normally it'll it'll get to it
it'll get it out of there but one of the
great advantages of this is nobody talks
about this this is such a huge thing
about has nothing to do with like muscle
strength or flexibility it's organ
health
and your endocrine I could talk about
this all
day but your endocrine system which is
one of the critical systems this is how
you know lymph gets around in your body
it's how if I remember
right um you know adrenal galand and all
that stuff there's there's a system for
chemical dispersion through your body
that doesn't have anything to do with
blood even though the circulatory system
is mostly blood
but all of those systems including your
heart system you your veins your veins
are designed to when you compress a vein
it pushes the blood up and then it has a
latch and it it closes so that the blood
can't go back people that get varicose
Spains those that kind of that's what's
gone they can't stop the blood from
going back and
pooling
but you know if you keep help healthy
veins and stuff
then you know you compress it in order
to use them the point is is that if you
compress something in the blood
system it'll push the blood
forward and it won't go back and then
the new blood will
come and if you're your liver and your
internal
organs when you compress them your
intestine too your gut it's actually
what after you do marasa one of the
reasons I really have to wait until I
use the restroom before I do
yoga because by doing that
rotation you whatever is in your
intestines is going to get squished out
and people will fart like crazy after
that uh I actually had a yoga teacher
who was teaching us yoga teachers she
goes and this is kind of an interesting
thing if you ever notice this if you
ever get stuck on the toilet she goes
just do a partial Mara a rotation of
your midsection and I guarantee you
she's like it'll it'll launch everything
out of you because you're because you're
basically you're you're basically
squeezing it out Minecraft
mode
e
e e
all right
back should be
back I had to fix a few things uhoh
kind of a blown
out scene there huh
we through the tunnel and see if we get
good reception or not
imagine we will
this have to push the
light cuz it doesn't ever give me
access what was
that what the was
that oh there's like a huge lip on this
[Music]
thing almost took me
down oh I hit that huge water
[Music]
thing oh The Crossing walks are out of
service
nice well
[Music]
I lowered my bike so that it picks up
the metal from the magnetic
detector most of them still do that
hey look at that it's changing for me
now cuz I did
that still works that old trick still
works and why wouldn't
it you have to have a metal frame for
that to work carbon frame it won't work
man we're making great time
today is it cuz I'm talking is that
why must be we're going through the
tunnel
victory scree
well we got much better reception
today in this area it was really janky I
guess the starlink does work I love that
bike it's so cute did you see that
[Music]
bike it was so cute
on the left
[Music]
baby for
another tunnel
bugs of the
lore hello
for
w
it's
[Applause]
oh
this is so
hard that's a big S on the
route it's a little one but it's like
straight up
[Music]
I should probably put the polarizing
filter back on the sun it'd be really
nice I REM me to buy one
again this little magnetic thing that
falls off easy
a go go
go up
[Music]
hey
baaba thank you for that phone
what's up with the Great
guess no starlink and no Verizon
there what are we doing how we going
why did that guy remind me of Dr Demento
does know anybody here know what that is
I seriously doubt
it Dr Demento
power walking
to power
walking classic
race walking race
walking I wasn't supposed to see it
because it was right at R CU it has all
those prostitutes in it and adult
themes why are we having issues
we should not be having
issues Amazon Prime this message bought
you buy another yet another Amazon
Prime you know what that was a that was
another transfer
issue because the modem's picked it up
and it's all good now it only happens
when the starlink dies and it has to
switch entirely over to
modem I still think it's worth it though
it the problem is in the transition
between the starlink and the
modems like when the mo when there's
absolutely no
starlink it seems that when the modem
dies and the starlink is available the
starlink will pick up the slack every
time but the reverse is not
true if if we go into an area where
there's pretty modest Verizon
coverage you know what it is is the
algorithm doesn't adapt fast enough
because it has to have been pushing a
certain amount of bandwidth before it
increments it its its level we need I
wish they would let us change the
algorithm and have it be
immediate because it has to say oh hey I
I got you know 800 fine so now I can go
to no 900 and then it takes about a
second for that to to ramp up so when
Starling cuts out at 4,000 KS per second
when it's like carrying the
load the the motivs don't have time to
ramp up and then you get the gray that's
what it say algorithm the balancing
algorithm is messed
up oh it's been working well in the past
yesterday so yesterday we had a
different problem there was no starlink
yesterday
yeah the only thing fundamentally
different for East Coast from when you
saw me on my trip is that I have two
modems
now there are you and that that
actually might might be complicating the
issue actually because that means that
the modems can carry more of the load so
there's more load that has to transfer
when staring goes away you know both of
the modems have to ramp
up yeah that's probably the
reason but I mean we had the opposite
problem yesterday right so yesterday I
tried going back to two
modems two modems
is that's what I've been using forever
right and I realized how spoiled I
gotten by the starlink picking up the
slack I was on starlink plus one
modem but there was almost no trees at
all so this transfer thing didn't happen
the thing where it transfers back and
forth between the two that didn't happen
like right now we got nice clear sky no
trees watch Starling could be busted
ass nope 3 kilobits per
second
huh but that's fine with me
because I don't want to burn up my
Starling bandwidth the only reason I
turn the Starling back on is to cover
the places where the the mum sucks ass
and I thought that we were going to be
totally clean here I thought that this
particular area was going to be clean
and it turned out that there like
five black hole
spots uh that starlink can cover so it's
like it's kind of like which one's worse
right having Starling cover those black
holes which are pretty substantial and
like all the greenway I watched today
that Greenway was completely unst
streamable yesterday you couldn't see
any of it low bit rate really
choppy and I I stream The Greenway no
problem today except for the tunnel
because starlink picked up the band
picked up because there's no Verizon
signal there there's bad Verizon signal
not low not
none I've been watching the stream all
day today and the stream the kilobits
per second it on average is way higher
so the quality the overall quality of
the the entire thing is super high
because the starlink is is boosting the
Verizon signal is even more by giving it
an extra 2K of of a bit rate and that
allows us to have really really
pretty uh there's like a lot less
compression artifacts and
stuff so it's worth it it's worth it to
have it but it's just kind of
interesting to note it's just kind of
interesting to note that
when when the starlink has been car
doing all the heavy lifting and it has
to switch back to the
Verizon uh it takes a while for the
Verizon to come back but the reverse is
not as true
apparently anyway
I mean if you go back you can go check
actually if you care I do if you
compare so I did exactly the same stream
same route and everything yesterday
pretty much slight deviation but pretty
much the same stream yesterday if you go
back and watch and compare and I
do cuz I care cuz I care about my people
they want to have a good thing hey
Joey so I oh my God somebody's
barbecuing oh that's what I love about
biking at this time of night God it
please invite me
over
um so yeah but if you care
about that kind of thing you can go back
and compare the streams and you can see
the difference in stream
quality and the overall uh so far I'm
actually I'm monitoring the stream right
now I I got a Bonus battery for my phone
so I can leave my phone monitor so I can
monitor the stream for my phone while
I'm while I'm doing it and I can already
see the quality is like way way better
so we have the pocket 3 that's the
difference and we have the Starling
today both of those things combined both
of the things combined have given us a
much better stream today very happy
about that but we did have a couple you
know brown outs and I was likeing what
the hell thought we fixed all those but
there's still a couple and they were
minimal so they're less than 2
seconds that's fine
it's a miracle any of this stuff even
works at all can you really think about
it hey
hi okay that was a little bit too much
the pocket 3 gim is such a such a win
though the bigger
sensor oh my God another Amazon Prime
truck how many is
that that's at least six
today if you count the person who didn't
have a truck just had the
vest I swear I should be a partner just
for all the Amazon Prime trucks I show I
swear to God
you will not find I am seriously I am
the number one streamer of Amazon Prime
trucks I should put that in my about
page good people at Amazon doing their
job
bringing us our
stuff I feel like this Sky could be
sharper it would be if I put the
polarizing filter rack on
I'm really debating about whether I
should get the
5 or
not the action 5 has better Horizon
balancing
so and it's
waterproof has the same sensor size as
the other one
though but apparently it's an upgraded
sensor I think it's the same one as this
pocket 3 but I can't prove that
spot checks I know I totally
could
Hardware I can't get it without the
battery the extra battery
for like
360 which is a lot cheaper than the
pocket the pocket's 600
the pocket 3 costs as much as like a
really nice digital SLR like a Canon
Rebel or something you or whatever you
want it's kind
of kind of an interesting price
point the the only reason I'm I mean I
have the cameras so I've already bought
them I don't need any
one
but could be a back I don't know yeah I
mean I have I have four cameras so
actually if you count my GoPros I got
seven
cameras I have oh actually if you count
my Cannon my Sony's the standard IRL
camera I have two of those
so yeah that's like 12 cameras 10
cameras something like
that so I have backup cover in fact I
have uh I have the action 4 with me
right now as a backup in case it
rains cuz it's totally waterproof I can
plug it in and be in in the middle of a
rainstorm it's fine the pocket 3 I
already did that it
breaks there's no way to waterproof
it at
all but I
mean the only reason I'm thinking of
getting it is because it apparently has
better stabilization and low light which
is the only reason I would get
it and it has really good Horizon
balancing so the one thing I don't like
about the pocket 3 on my
chest is like when I bend
over it doesn't it doesn't stay
centered it follows
me and I don't want to do that I want it
to stay
locked and there's no way to do
that there's no way to make it do
that and it's got a better S Ser so
we should go out and eat
tonight I don't know when my wife's
coming home
come on I know I wanted to do
that people have been asking the Bell on
the Bell locks for him for that of a
long time he hasn't added
it you could do it but it would
be really out of
sync you know what I
mean it would be really out of
sync because
the the both of them would be coming up
to completely different
intervals people do all the time they'll
stream from their phone and then they'll
also stream from their Bell
box yeah
God this app is so broken
[Applause]
why would you do
that good thing you didn't run me over
we got to to our right what are we doing
you're going to wait for me
Odin
Santa Odin Santa what the who the hell
is that I don't
know lots of stuff going on down here
[Music]
it's Friday man it's Friday and it's
like the most popular time of the
[Music]
night Prime
Time wait who is that that drove their
Jeep up there are they trying to sell
their Jeep or something
by
we get out ice
cream I don't think I don't think Mina's
here anymore I think she I think closes
the places she used to work she used to
work right there and she's she's gone
now
yeah so we go get that ice
cream I we should we get dinner should
we get dinner should we get beer or
should we just get ice cream we should
probably get dinner we should probably
go to cabba and go get dinner there get
like an actual meal what do you think
should we go get an actual meal at
[Music]
Cava oh my God it's a cyber
truck I kind of want to stay here and
see who comes out of it
I really
do that's the biggest to
buy that I'm sorry it's so
stupid I kind of want to Burger
something's going on down here though we
just get burgers I wonder what Doris is
going to do I I should call her last
time I almost went and got food and she
made a huge
meal yeah there was like a huge meal
waiting a good guy with a CIO
oo they got like they got like a web
bar they're making like martinis and
stuff yeah
it's
only
[Music]
you kind of want
Starbucks what you head oh baby what you
love
[Music]
oh cop I thought it was going to come
after
me let's go get something in Davidson
support something in our local community
community we could go buy more pink
underwear I'm out my other pink
underwear needs to be
refreshed we go buy more pink underwear
in Victoria
Secret I feel like there's more sun
glare now than there was
before can't quite put my finger on it
though yeah definitely need the
polarizing culture ooh Canadian
geese but they're flying North what the
hell wrong guy wrong way
guys
yeah this town here yeah we've had more
sun I don't know I just feel like the
image is not as rich as it has been in
the past so I can't can't explain it I'm
watching the
monitor I don't
know I'm going to turn it
could
be yeah this look a little Dusty
I have no
idea we call
her car
right hello hi I am streaming just so
you
know okay what's
up I am working on my credit card
reconciliation and then I'm going to
Good Year oh that's right you have the
Good Year show tonight
okay all right so I'm just I'm Justified
going out tonight if I go out absolutely
I'm not going to be I'm not going to be
crazy but where are you going I don't
know maybe Sushi I'll brush my teeth
when you get
home all right or something else what
else shower huh you better shower I'm
I'm I always shower honey um should we
should we do actually I could do Burger
instead bur sounds
better
anyway I do want to I'm not going to be
that late cuz I'm not I don't want to oh
okay so you're still going to have an
hour to snuggle or something I'll be
home by I'll be home by 8 so we we can
watch an episode or
two yeah okay yeah I'll be home by have
to make dinner when I get home just so
you know well actually I can do the soup
I can eat leftovers if you go e um yeah
you could eat up the stew um I ate all
the lentils
so I need ground beef we could just make
burgers when I get home that's a great
idea that's a great idea then I'll just
I'll have a smoothie when I get home and
then when you get home we'll have
burgers out that late Burgers okay
tomorrow tomorrow I need to go to uh
pick up the rest of my smoothie
ingredients and but but I'll have a
protein smoothie when I come home I'll
be actually looking forward to that now
so I'm glad I called you you're always
right not always right but thank you you
were right about this like yesterday I
almost went out and eat but then I came
home and there was this glorious Indian
meal waiting so there you go um awesome
are you going to do you want to get the
meat or do you want me to I don't have a
actually I do I can just strap it to my
huh what do you want me to get the
meat what are you on your bike yeah I
can stop and get it it's okay I mean I
do have a front rack so I can no I'll go
get it all righty that's on my way all
right don't don't you dare grab beer
okay no I don't want I'm very weak right
now right now I'm very weak that beer
looks so freaking good and I want to
avoid it so I'm going to go get a
smoothie instead okay all right bye
bye I love
her she's awesomest she's the
awesomest Nico thank you for the follow
I kind of consider
myself a moving camera
rig the fact that I'm on the bike is
kind of
immaterial it's more about the
camera you
know that's generally the vibe that I'm
going for
go to interesting places and just be the
mobile
camera she is tired she's been working
her ass off man my wife is a hard
worker so funny a couple years ago she
didn't even have a job
there and now she's like second or third
in command pretty much they had to
cancel meetings one day because she
wasn't
there that's always a good
thing you get to that point in your
career the company can't function
without you literally I mean normally
that's considered a bad thing in Tech
you always you never want that you
always want to prepare
contingencies because you're more like a
firefighter oh you couldn't put that
fire out cuz I wasn't there uh sucks you
better have me there then next time bad
idea all the firefighters need to be
trained so they can save lives equally
well that's my job I'm not a firefighter
but sort of
am not her though she's she's more in
the art career path thingy so being you
know an essential member of the team job
security absolutely in technology if you
if you create a system where you're the
only one who can maintain it because you
think it's job security let me promise
you it is not I have talked to several
people including a c who I'm very close
friends with um who shared stories over
drinks
about they were really really sad they
even cried about it they cried because
it was so
bad it was so bad it got so bad it got
so
dramatic and there was so much on the
line
there was so much on the line the whole
system could have gone down and then she
would they would have lost her
job
so if you're that person if you think if
you have the inkling of a thought that
says I'm going to write this in some
esoteric language that nobody else knows
because that'll make me you know they'll
never be able to fire me after that if
you work that way you will die your
career will
die I promise you eventually will catch
up with you I've seen it happen over and
over
again people who try to do
that and then they get a bad
reputation your reputation is
solid your reputation is
solid Malcolm Reynolds gets it done they
say you don't want a solid reputation
that's bad in Tech you just really don't
on Twitch or YouTube fine on te on in in
the industry no you just do not want
that who knows who Nisa
is do you know who Nisa
is I'm using references that very always
very special people will get I'm just
kind of a filter I want to see who knows
who knows who Nisa
is from a very
famous series give you that
hint people that I don't
care Nisa
yeah I'll give you another
hint that quote contained a name in it
and the name was Malcolm
Reynolds that kind of gives it
away thank
you French rapper
no I mentioned m i did kind of didn't I
tell tall sorry
yeah all right who I'll give you here's
another one who is the
name what is the
name of the person that also calls
themselves Mrs Malcolm
Reynolds we'll play some trivia
n NCO was kind of on the edge there it
wasn't a tow it was
right yeah yeah you got it I Kip of
course looked it
up another Amazon Prime truck that's at
least eight that's eight Amazon Prime
trucks we have to see we got to start
counting and see what is our what is the
maximum Amazon Prime trucks we've seen
in one shot here's one of those guys
with L
Car yes we all know you have a small
penis
who is Mrs Malcolm
Reynolds is Ja we kind of could oh
that would be so much fun is that
illegal oh how much how much how
many bits to do that I really want to do
that
people think I have a bomb on my back I
start I walk up start tamming Amazon
Prime trucks beds are going to show
up
right that is a great idea though I so
want to do
that how can we do that legally
this is such a good
idea who is known as the father of
yoga that's know who you talk to
but there most people would say t Kish
macharia
most people that's what they would say
they would be
[Music]
wrong I think it's uh fanali fanali
Y how he going to say they mentioned
patang in the opening Mantra should we
see it let see the opening mon now for
the hell of
it but pangali is in the opening
Mantra opening aaga Mantra yeah
ohas PR
oh
Shanty shanty
Shanty W even
fly mfly
you de
McFly McFly for
president everybody left I started
chanting and 12 people's Abandoned
Ship I'm out of here
it's better if I just shut my
mouth I'm sitting here watching the the
viewers I can see the viewer count as it
updates
it's it's really
fun of course it doesn't update in real
time I wish it did I should probably
make a widget for
that I I do I like I do like doing
things and seeing which things piss
people off and people look away it's
really kind of interesting information
to know I really don't care but it's
it's kind of
fun I just like the study of human
nature you know
name Co
conspirators I know oh that's what it
was we were talking about
tagging that's your right that was like
before the the Indian
stuff yeah I think you're right I think
you know that we were talking about
taging Amazon trucks and wearing a
bomb it's a pretty cool looking
bomb where's Bellum that should go in my
quotes list
going to get in total trouble for that
one this house to our right was struck
by
lightning about 10 minutes before we
passed it it was still on
fire the trucks were here putting it out
and
everything in the back it's actually the
it's actually the the the house on the
back they got lit on fire the grandma
house or whatever
the
garage so no people hurt it was pretty
intense though that yeah that's one of
the reasons I want to put
um I want to do storm chasing on the
bike yeah wouldn't that be fun cuz why
not right I'm totally hooked up for
it if I put my fenders on this bike if I
put my
Army thing over my rack my my I put
weather guard on my camera we could go
storm chasing on the
bike
or the storms tend to chase me though so
I don't really have to go chasing them
they usually find me and there's good
video of that by the way there's really
good video the first the first trip to
Charlotte got totally rained out and I
think there's a clip of
me uh accepting a
rain poncho from a guy under a
bridge yeah that was a good day I
couldn't see anything though I was
wearing this hat and it just rained it
just soaked right through just went all
the way through that was when I realized
why people put those plastic things on
their hats you know why the cops and
people always put the plastic covers on
their on their baseball CS like doesn't
the cap just keep the r out it
absolutely doesn't once it gets soaked
it just conveys the water right into
your eyes it's all
salty so you got to if you're going to
wear a baseball cap you got to get
yourself that reminds me I got to buy
one I don't think a Ziploc bag is going
to cover
it oh look neigh hood neighorhood kidss
are playing
something what are they
playing
hi I got so it's like that reminds me of
my
childhood always playing something
interesting
outside if you can't see them they can't
see you exactly
I should probably turn my light on as
you mention
it I don't know how to make it blink
there we go
[Music]
our race a little
high it's still in zone to but
did you hear
that I hope
not that's what you get when you have
lentils for
lunch not tired I'm not the
today I'm not I'm
thirsty I'm not
tired no I don't know
why I'm just getting used to it
again I think yesterday I had a lot of
stress because of all the bouncing on
the camera it made me stress out so I'm
like really chill
today cuz I'm using it on you know on my
back and I can see the the the feed
so that's actually a really hard thing
to do as a live streamer to see it to a
point where you can just chill out and
just live and have fun you know because
you do you get so stressed out about all
the logistics of the live streaming
stuff that you stop enjoying what you're
doing it's one of the reasons people
give it up that's why I
did
but you know now that I've got the rig
back on my back and I know it works and
I can literally monitor the feed while
it's happening so if something goes
wrong I know
immediately
that makes a guy like me able to relax
and just enjoy the ride and I really
have I really enjoyed this ride today
I need to get my Blinky red light out
though put that on my bike I'm going to
put it on my
Fender this little section that we're
going to be on right here is like one of
the few sections that it's a pretty tame
section I can go as fast as the cars but
there's lots and lots of
cars I'm not I I don't mind this section
at
all fact there's really no section of
this ride that scares me
really they're all super
mellow
but I mean there were before we
discovered the tunnel crossing the
highway that was always a tough one that
was a little bit scary every time
I have not stopped at Cho Bell in days I
know cuz I'm on the bike I'm I'm all
eating brush now yeah East Coast I've
been I've been
eating I've been drinking uh Citrus uh
green smoothies every morning and
protein smothie at lunch I've been doing
guacamole mostly P based since I got
back I gave up alcohol I had bow with
alcohol
there uh a little bit then I gave it all
up I'm really hoping I have I have a
case of nielo left to finish off back in
the apartment after that that's it I'm
going to try to
go I'm going to try to go no alcohol
there just too much information about it
that's green
buddy I don't know what you're looking
at he's looking at me is what he's
looking at
I know you know what it's funny you say
that I we brought my blunch on my
honeymoon
camping cuz I was I had to have guac
every day and I had to have my smoothie
every
day I'm thinking of buying another one
we've had this bunte since
so it's
old more than 12 years old it's getting
kind of loud I think it probably needs a
work like it the needs to some oil
they probably have it
serviced It's a Wonderful blender I love
it this little section always makes me
feel a little bit like a bike messenger
in New York or
something obviously not but a
little you better not turn unless you're
get a
signal the problem with the Smoothie
makers you have to be able to find fruit
and food for the
smoothie and it's such a food
desert they do weave I normally I do
though I'm not doing it right now
normally when I'm on the road bike I'm
in the middle of the road
here when the road when this the stop
step comes up I do the bike messenger
thing but I promis myself I'm going to
keep my heart rate in the green zone or
lower so I can do this every
day yeah that I actually looked at it I
almost bought a cooler to put all the
fruit in and stuff but then you know
that's a one less area in my Subaru that
you can live
in I'm not ruling it out
but next year's trip is going to be all
on the bike whatever is I do next year
it's going to be maybe two weeks of
vacation it's going to be all on the
bike I'll stay in hotels and stuff but
it'll be bike
ribbon this is always
dangerous there's a hot
place oh my God it's first Friday
there's a huge thing going on tonight I
totally forgot about it yeah there's
like a massive massive event happening
right
now I totally
forgot we'll go down and take a
peek I used to live right here
I used to live in that in that town home
right there the one that says hope and
freedom which is such
but
whatever I think today's for Friday I
think oh no take it back must be there
it must be the cane Center's got an
event starting up they they put that's a
against everybody's wishes they went
ahead and put that thing up anyway
that's the cane Center for Performing
Arts you know why I did that because
Performing Arts makes more money
they literally called the the artwork
and the sculpture that my wife was doing
the dirty arts and my my wife and Renee
G and a bunch of people they always
quote that should we go by the comic
Place Let's Ride by we got some
time my wife said she's home at 8
tonight
so can fr is horrible all the vitamins
are
gone Frozen fresh or
nothing they don't like it when I take
my camera in there cuz there's a bunch
of shy comic book little Warcraft Magic
the Gathering
40K people in there
Warhammer they do not like the
camera I tried that once and I learned
my
lesson it's green what do you
know that was
lucky that never
happens can't
Cactus smoothie I have
not I have no intention of having one
are they that
good let's get on the trail it's kind of
fun it's still have sunlight I won't be
able to do the trail in the dark
eventually I have to stay on the
road hello hi
something is making a
noise gu is very tall
line
corner
Ow like a line out to grab
somebody freckly pear smoothie huh
huh I mean why not
[Music]
woo
uh-oh somebody lost their
shirt literally
Elementary School up here
I must be bus
zones pink
purple nice ball
there
turn them off season's over
so water stuff is turned
on yeah that's a working plug outlet I
got to remember that
okay see the camera couldn't do this I
see dead
people who aren't
dead baseball fields
Saddler portable classroom
yes gresly paved Rich Boomer
roads this is Rich hippie row that's
what I call
it rich hippies
bunch of really rck wickedly Rich
hippies over
there beautiful huh I like this area way
better than the golf hores
area still is kind of
obnoxious how much money people spend on
stuff the person on the corner has
a a little garage for their bikes that's
how hippie they are
see right there like a little shed I see
out there working on the riks all the
time only one out right now maybe
they're riding
them I might keep that little Loop in
the in the normal route cuz it takes the
edge off that Hill it's a pretty killer
otherwise hi
there renting storage
yeah I
know the
garage I
agree I know that's one of the reasons
we got a place in just rented storage my
wife has her her Studio to put stuff in
I wasn't going to comment but since you
did
I you see she turned around I knew I
knew if I did she'd
know I
did she was exceptionally
yummy I imagine she's a very
hardworking doesn't socialize very
much absolutely brilliant she's probably
David in college
full
scholarship that's what my guess is oh
it's
it's it's full pedestrian
so that means I can
go man there's a lot of people out
tonight she can your typing no I'm
always afraid though I almost know want
to mention it my sound is on though so
if somebody were to do a sticker at the
right time
I was like oh my sound is anytime I
come up on a person like
that I always worry about that because
you
know but I made the stickers to cost a
little bit more money
so people have to pay a buck for to
humiliate me I'm good with that
oh wait all right let's turn around and
go
back so we can end the
stream almost went home before ending
the
stream there's the Davidson Art Gallery
Museum to the left that's where our good
friends live and work horses
friends
really get a Muffler
dude seriously your engine is not work
showing off it's too
[Music]
tiny it's like it's like you sound like
one of those little yappy dogs it's like
really loud compared to like Sam he just
doesn't say anything
Sigma
energy it's impossible to project Sigma
energy with a loud
car you just sound like a yappy
dog I know that was mean to say but it's
true seeing you
like ended up crashing into a
table or not we're about to far point we
always stop at the same place
so I'll go ahead and do that
now go try to find somebody to
raid let's see what do we do today
2 hours and 19 minutes that's not bad
it's 15 minutes faster than was was
suggested by
whatever 26 miles okay that part I
knew all right let's uh send you on your
way shall
[Music]
we what's
that oh you want to raid them yeah ULU
Mah yeah for sure let's do
that I'm happy to have you guys guide
The Raid I I I hate finding people to
raid it's like my single least favorite
thing to do so if you have people to
raid please suggest
them love it love love love it
how do you spell that
again ULU ULU
mic start raid
raid has then started Cali streamer nice
he's not in San
Diego how
refreshing if you know what I mean
right
wait how
refreshing that's my favorite Indian
place
I guess we'll see you guys
tomorrow
[Music]
um yeah I might actually stream a little
bit when I get home maybe not I'm going
to get home and bu some do some coding
and stuff I might go ahead and stream
that just for a little bit like a short
stream um tomorrow I am just doing yoga
in the morning and the biking at night
but I'm not streaming anything else I
don't think I'm going to be cleaning the
apartment and new moving so I don't know
how how up for streaming I'm going to be
tomorrow probably not very
much
so see you
guys have a great one